Black faces in high places are not going to save us.
Just look at the black proponents of Cop City in Atlanta's leadership class.
Just look at the black woman's hand, ambassador at the UN, voting against a ceasefire in Gaza.
Our blackness and our womanness are not in themselves trustworthy.
If we allow ourselves to be conscripted into positions of power that maintain the oppressive status quo.
Our blackness and womanness are not themselves trustworthy if we support the occupation of black neighborhoods with so-called better trained police.
Or remain silent about the genocide of oppressed peoples around the world funded by our tax dollars.
And here, let me please shout out the incredible Spelman students and AUC siblings who have been organizing with Stop Cop City and Justice in Palestine, among many other troublemakers in this room.
You all remind us that college is not a waiting room to enter the real world, but that you can start transforming that world right here, right now.
It goes without saying, but let me just say it anyway.
For student activists speaking out courageously for Palestine and Congo and Haiti and to stop Cop City, they should not be threatened with expulsion, loss of scholarships, or have public safety called on them for protesting.
Too often our institutions celebrate student activists after they've graduated, even giving them honorary degrees, activism while we are enrolled.